I know that you're thinking I really don't need to,
but I want to say it again.
S-Say what?
I love you, Kiriyama Yui-san.
Will you go out with me?
H-Hold on, what's this all about?
I already turned you down.
But my feelings haven't changed.
And you can always change y—
No!
I can't!
Not yet.
"Yet"?
You know, I've always been curious.
Why me?
Iori's a lot cuter than I am,
and Inaba's just plain beautiful.
There's plenty of good things about you too.
But it's mostly just a feeling.
When I met you, I knew I would fall in love with you.
And I did fall in love with you.
That hasn't changed.
Why'd you pick a time like this to tell me?
Yui, how do you feel about Taichi?
About Taichi?
I...
I love him.
As a friend.
A-And what about me?
I hate you as a friend.
No way!
I'm obviously joking!
I probably love you more than I hate you.
But just as a friend! A friend!
That's as much as I can say right now.
Sorry.
It's not that I don't like you.
I just can't go out with anyone right now.
What a relief. So I still have a chance!
Is that all you wanted?
Let's go back and have lunch.
Is that an invitation to eat with you?
No.
I have friends waiting for me.
Hey, wait!
And just so you know, Taichi ranks way higher than you on my male friend list.
How'd you know about this?
What?! I knew it!
Taichi's my biggest rival!
When I switched with Yui yesterday, I saw a text from Aoki.
Accidentally, of course.
So,
I thought it might be good to give you two some stimulation.
"Stimulation"?
Well, what you do next is up to you.
See you.
Let's go back too.
I'm okay.
Just you, Taichi?
Yeah.
Wait, are you Inaba?
Yeah, that's right.
Iori and I switched bodies.
So...
what did you think about Aoki and Yui at lunch?
What did I think?
It felt like they were in a different world.
Inaba, what were you hoping to accomplish by showing us that?
Don't tell me you really can't figure it out!
Huh?
Whatever. I'll get right to the point.
Taichi, how do you feel about Iori?
You just keep slinging these blunt questions.
And asking this one from Nagase's body is just...
Perfect timing, right?
What's perfect about it?
Well...
I really like the way we are right now.
I don't want to ruin it, but—
Oh, just you two?
Inaban, that was too fast.
I tricked you, silly.
Iori!
Taichi, what the hell did you do?!
I don't know!
Nagase pretended she switched with you!
Pretended she switched? Why would she?
I don't know why eith—
No matter what happens...
no matter who you pretend to be...
I'll always know who you are.
Looks like you do know why.
Yeah, and that I'm a complete idiot.
She wanted to trust me.
Need a good punch to the face?
Yeah, could y—
Shut up and go after her!
This is between you and her.
Fujishima!
Yaegashi-kun?
Have you seen Nagase?
Perhaps it's the way of the world for couples to only be a man and a woman.
What do you think?
I don't have time for that kind of talk!
I need to find Nagase—
Get out of the way, Fuji—
Nagase-san ran out the main gate.
She didn't need me.
I'm sure the one Nagase-san needs is you.
Fujishima, are you sure about this?
If you're who Nagase-san needs right now,
then of course.
Now, go on.
Nagase,
where are you?
Nagase!
Taichi?
I'm sorry that I didn't realize it was you!
I even promised you, but...
What are people? What is the "self"?
So long as you look like someone else, no one can tell who's really on the inside.
Oh, it's not like I'm trying to make you feel bad.
This was definitely all my fault, anyway.
I'm really sorry.
But that's because you wanted
to try moving on, right?
Thanks.
And now, it's my turn.
Um...
How should I put this?
I really wish I could be more like you.
More like me?
I can't show my emotions the way you do.
Being happy, being angry, being sad...
That's why I wish I could be more like you and show that I'm enjoying my life.
That's just me putting on different personalities.
You said that the other day, too.
But were you really just pretending?
What?
What are you trying to say?
Maybe there's something you didn't understand?
Screwing around, playing innocent, getting embarrassed, telling dirty jokes...
Going along with any joke, but actually planning it all out.
Not thinking some things through, yet completely overthinking other things.
Telling jokes before a serious talk so it doesn't look like you're embarrassed.
And sometimes looking like you don't feel anything at all.
What are you talking about?
They're all you.
What part of that is me?
They're all Nagase Iori!
A person like that can't exist.
No one has that many faces!
I'd say that it's totally normal.
Everyone has different faces.
I don't have many.
You have a lot.
Isn't that all it boils down to?
But I change mine depending on who—
Everyone changes how they act depending on who's around them.
But I tell myself that I'm going with a certain personality!
You think people can deal with others without telling themselves what to do?
But I can even change what I like depending on the mood!
I couldn't even choose a club for myself!
That just means you like a lot of things.
And not choosing a club is no different than joining a club that looked easy.
You can't prove any of that.
Yeah.
Starting somewhere in the middle.
You know,
I wish I could be more like you too.
You know exactly who you are.
No matter who I pretend to be, you'll always be you.
I wish I could be someone who could make people feel secure like that.
Nagase.
I love you, Nagase Iori.
Will you go out with me?
Um...
Hello. Long time no see.
You've probably already realized this, but I'm...
Balloon Vine?
Yes.
Well, I'll apologize ahead of time.
Sorry.
But the fault lies with all of you.
You're all much too interesting.
Wait... What are you...
I've already apologized.
Nagase!
Yes. Please.
Where's Gossan?
He'll be here soon.
Looks like they got a hold of Iori's mom too.
Well, hello there.
You...
What do you want now?
Nagase Iori-san's body will die soon.
What the hell?!
Are you saying you can control people's lives?
Of course I can't do that.
But I can know exactly what the reality of the situation is.
Who would believe anything you say?!
Whether you believe me or not is your choice to make.
Now then...
Are you ready?
Listen closely.
I'd like you all to decide whose personality will die with Nagase-san's body.
You mean...
For the next 30 minutes, I'll make it so that
you can switch personalities at will by stating who switches with whom.
That's all.
You...
Our lives are not your toys!
Taichi!
Do you understand?
Your 30-minute window starts now.
Basically,
he's telling us to choose who to kill.
But I don't want Iori to die!
The doctors are doing everything they can too!
Yeah. He could've been lying,
but there's also a chance he wasn't.
Either way, we have to deal with the situation.
Whether we like it or not.
If...
If someone has to be a sacrifice,
then I'll do it.
Shut the hell up.
Who asked you to be a sacrifice?!
Have you ever stopped to think about the people you're sacrificing yourself for?
You may look like you're thinking about others,
but you're really only thinking about yourself!
You're nothing but a selfish freak!
Well, sorry!
Yeah, I hate seeing people getting hurt!
When I imagine how they'll suffer,
it just gets worse and worse!
It hurts me more than anything else!
I hate that!
It's better if I get hurt instead!
At least I know how much it'll hurt!
I can put up with it!
You're right.
I'm not doing it for anyone else.
I'm being a selfless freak for myself!
I see.
You really are crazy.
You're crazy,
but you're crazy in a nice way.
You want to help, but you can only hurt yourself. You're such an idiot. Seriously.
But you should know how much it hurts us then.
I think that Iori-chan has to die with her body.
What are you saying?!
I didn't want to say it,
but someone had to.
Either way, we need to tell Iori-chan.
Yeah.
I made the suggestion, so I'll switch.
I, Aoki Yoshifumi, want to switch with Nagase Iori.
Um...
Why are you all here?
I was just on the bridge, talking to Taichi...
Iori,
try to stay calm and listen.
Right now...
Then...
I guess I'll just have to die.
Nagase, it doesn't have to be that way!
It can't be any other way.
Killing another personality and taking their body is a sin.
One too heavy for me to live with.
Where's my mom?
She's on her way here.
I see.
Um...
Can I... have a word with each of you before I go?
Taichi...
Iori wants to talk to you next.
Yo, Taichi!
Hey, Nagase.
Huh? You look the same as always.
I don't show much emotion, after all.
First of all, Taichi...
Thanks.
My problems don't seem as grave after talking to you.
It feels like I can actually love myself now.
You said that you love me, right?
I want to respond to your feelings now.
But wouldn't you like to hear a joke before that?
Not really, but I thought you might tell one.
How can you act so much like you always do?
Everyone else was really sad.
I'm sad too.
So sad I could die.
But you're sadder than me.
If I cried, you couldn't cry yourself.
I don't want to die.
I want to keep living.
I had so much to look forward to.
Why?
Why does this have to happen to me?
What did I do wrong?
You even told me that you love me.
I love you too, Taichi.
So please, don't go out with me.
I mean, I'm going to die soon.
It wouldn't be good for you to go out with me now.
You think that m—
Instead, give me a memory.
Maybe we...
could kiss?
I'm sure Inaban will forgive us.
It's time for your answer.
Who will it be?
Me.
Nagase Iori will die with Nagase Iori's body.
Well, that's the obvious choice.
Can I ask you one last question?
This is something I have to ask.
You won't do this to anyone else, right?
Of course.
Oh, it's time.
Iori?!
Wait...
Don't tell me it's over!
We were very lucky.
She's okay now.
There shouldn't be any permanent damage.
We'll let you see her soon.
All right, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Have these.
It's my way of apologizing.
It's also for Nagase-san when she wakes up.
We've been had...
I thought it was a possibility, but...
Then Iori's safe?
She's alive?
Thank goodness.
How much of this was planned?
Well, you could say it was planned from start to finish.
That's how the story goes.
I think we can do a lot more than you think we can.
You didn't plan on hurting Nagase at all from the start?
We can't cause that kind of trouble for a normal, good person.
I even made sure her cell phone didn't get wet.
I won't ask you to forgive me,
but I hope you won't hate me.
After all, this experience was to your benefit.
Until next time.
Congratulations!
Thanks!
Sorry to make you worry about me.
No need to sweat that!
Did anything else weird happen to you guys?
Nothing.
We haven't switched personalities since.
It looks like it's all over now.
I hope so.
For now, let's just eat.
Aoki, make some tea.
Okay! Got it!
Have a seat, Iori-chan.
Thanks.
I kind of feel bad, though.
Come on, Taichi!
Inaba!
Get to work!
Oh, right.
When I went to visit Iori, she told me...
Looks like you took my first kiss.
How should I make you pay me back?